Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Buttons and Memorabilia Collection, 1940-1990 IBT0057
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Gift of Cheryl Johnson, 1981-2006; Series 5
  - "Buy American" IBT Logo Lapel Pin with Name Panel: Cheryl Johnson, Local 20, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 23)
  - IBT Logo Magnet, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 24)
  - IBT Logo with Gold, White & Blue Enamel Keychain, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 25)
- Gift of Leo Deaner, 1971-2001; Series 7
  - Riker Mount Containing 1971 IBT Convention Buttons, Series 7 (Box 10, Item 1)
    Contains Frank E. Fitzsimmons and Thomas E. Flynn Campaign Buttons
  - Riker Mount Containing 1991 IBT Convention Buttons, Series 7 (Box 10, Item 2)
    Contains R.V. Durham, Bob Simposn, Hackett, and Feinstein Campaign Buttons
  - Riker Mount Containing 1991 IBT Convention Pins - Part 2, Series 7 (Box 10, Item 3)
    Contains Campaign Buttons for Shea Liguroits, Eddie Kornegay, Frank Carracino, John P. Morris, and Ron Carey
  - Riker Mount Containing 2001 Hoffa Campaign Buttons, Series 7 (Box 10, Item 4)
    Contains Anti-TDU, Hoffa/Keegel, Hoffa/Singer, Hoffa/Young, Bill Hogan, and Bouvier/McLean/Zimmerman (Teamsters Canada) Campaign Buttons
  - Riker Mount Containing Teamsters DRIVE Buttons and Pins, Undated; Series 7 (Box 10, Item 5)
  - Riker Mount Containing Strikes/Solidarity Days Buttons, 1963-1991; Series 7 (Box 10, Item 6)
  - Riker Mount Containing Miscellaneous Teamster Pins Part 1, Undated; Series 7 (Box 10, Item 7)
    Contains a selection of Local Chapter Pins, Dues Buttons, and Political Pins
  - Riker Mount Containing Miscellaneous Teamster Pins Part 2, Undated; Series 7 (Box 10, Item 8)
    Contains a selection of Division Pins, Event Pins, and Teamsters Logo Pins
  - Eastern Conference of Teamsters Vest, 1986; Series 7; Red vest printed with IBT Logo and "Presser and Mathis in '86" on front; "Vote the Team: Trerotola, McCarthy, Cleveland, Schurr, Shea, Cozza, Durham" on back (Box 10, Item 9)
  - Small Riker Mount Containing Eastern Conference of Teamsters Patch, Keychain and Pins, Undated; Series 7 (Box 10, Item 10)
- Gift of William A. Moore, 1935-2013; 1990-2006; Series 1
  This series consists of buttons, lapel pins, small memorabilia items such as keychains and pocket flashlights, and several larger items of memorabilia related to local union #696 including gavels and a framed Jimmy Hoffa shadowbox. Items were donated by local #696 organizer Bill Moore.
  - Local Union 165 Topeka, Kansas - 100 year anniversary lapel pin, 1999; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Voice of American Labor - Teamsters Vote 2000 Lapel Pin, Series 1 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - 27th Teamsters Convention Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 3)
  - Organizing for Power Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - We Support our Troops Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 5)
  - Union Yes Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 6)
  - Teamsters Logo American Flag Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 7)
  - Teamsters Port Division Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 8)
  - Canadian Maple Leaf Teamsters Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 9)
  - A Woman's Place is in Her Union (Rosie the Riveter) Lapel Pins, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 10a-c)
  - Teamsters Logo "Pride" Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 11)
  - Spirit of '76 American Flags Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 12a-b)
  - Local 986 Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 13)
  - Local 795 Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 14)
  - Teamsters and American Flag Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 15)
  - Newspaper, Magazine, Electronic Media Division Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 16)
  - Local 710 Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 17)
  - Motion Picture Division Lapel Pins, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 18a-b)
  - Local 190 (Billings, MT) Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 19)
  - Construction Division Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 20)
  - Teamsters Logo Sky Blue Enamel Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 21)
  - Teamsters Logo Gold Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 22)
  - Local 878 (Little Rock, AR) Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 23)
  - "Joint Council 26" Local 38 Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 24)
  - Local 959 (Fairbanks, AK) Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 25)
  - "10 Years" Teamsters Logo Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 26)
  - "Unions Care!" AFL-CIO Lapel Pin, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 27)
  - "Overroad Transfer - Grocery, Market, Cold-Storage, Drivers, Helpers and Inside Employees" 544 Buttons 1963-1964, Series 1 (Box 1, Item 28a-f)
  - "Overroad Transfer - Grocery, Market, Cold-Storage, Drivers, Helpers and Inside Employees" 544 Buttons 1970, Series 1 (Box 1, Item 29a-c)
  - "Overroad Transfer - Grocery, Market, Cold-Storage, Drivers, Helpers and Inside Employees" 544 Buttons 1973, Series 1 (Box 1, Item 30a-b)
  - "Kick Overnite's Ass" Button, 1999; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 31)
  - Young Hoffa 2001 Button, Series 1 (Box 1, Item 32)
  - "Unity in 2002" Button, Series 1 (Box 1, Item 33)
  - Local 544 Picnic Button, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 34)
  - A Woman's Place is in Her Union (Local 696) Button, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 35)
  - Hoffa Now! 100 Member Club Button, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 36)
  - A Woman's Place is in Her Union Button, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 37)
  - Respect is a Teamster Contract Button, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 38)
  - Teamsters 1st Button, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 39)
  - "Part-Time UPS Worker Full-Time Teamster" Button, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 40)
  - "UPS Show Me the Money" Button, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 41)
  - Respect is a Teamster Contract Buttons, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 42a-c)
  - "Nickel an Hour for Teamster Power" Button, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 43)
  - "Working Women Vote" Button, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 44)
  - "RISE Teamsters Running a Clean Union" Buttons, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 45a-b)
  - Teamsters Logo Embroidered Patch, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 46)
  - Teamsters Logo Small Patch, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 47)
  - Local 115 Embroidered Patch, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 48)
  - "God Grant me Serenity" Teamsters Logo Keychain, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 49)
  - Roy Williams JC 66 Dedication Keychain, 1967; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 50)
  - Plexiglass Teamsters Logo Keychain, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 51)
  - Local 731 Keychain, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 52)
  - National Freight Division Keychain, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 53)
  - Motion Picture Division Keychain, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 54)
  - "JRHMSF" Golf Keychain, 2012; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 55)
  - Brewery and Soft Drink Conference Keychains, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 56a-d)
  - Central Conference Keychain w/ Pocketknife & Clippers, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 57)
  - Minnesota Joint Council Money Clip/Pocket Knife, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 58)
  - Local 120 Golf Divot Tool, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 59)
  - Teamsters Hispanic Caucus Flashlight Keychain, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 60)
  - IBT Human Rights Commission "Help Erase Hate" Dry-Erase Tool, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 61)
  - Local 696 Pen Holder, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 62)
  - Industrial Trades Division 26th Convention Zipper Pouch, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 63)
  - IBT Logo Luggage Tag, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 64)
  - "Fight Smart and Win!" Office of Strategic Initiatives Magnet, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 65)
  - Local 120 2013-2014 Mini Calendar, Series 1 (Box 1, Item 66)
  - Local 891 2013-2014 Mini Calendar, Series 1 (Box 1, Item 67)
  - Sheet Metal Workers' International Association Rulers, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 68a-c)
  - Local 120 Deck of Cards, Series 1 (Box 1, Item 69a-b)
  - Local 544 Deck of Cards, Unknown; Series 1 (Box 1, Item 70)
  - "Teamster Joint Council 56, Roy L. Williams" Glass Plates, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Item 1a-b)
  - Teamsters and IBT Logo Lanyard, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - "International Brotherhood of Teamsters" Lanyards, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Item 2a-b)
  - Local 823, Joplin MO, Rulers, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Item 3a-c)
  - "1996 Hoffa - Restore the Power" Child's T-Shirt, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Item 4)
  - Tuscon, AZ Office of the Mayor, Proclamation granting Honorary Citizen Status to Teamsterettes of Topeka KS - Etched Copper Sheet, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Item 5)
  - Two Gavels from Local Union 696, 1935-2013; Series 1 (Box 3, Item 6a-b)
    Biographical / Historical
    These two gavels are from the 1930's and 1940's from Teamsters Local Union #696 northern half of State of Kansas. Used by principal officers: Harley Suthard - 1935-1948; LaRue A "Bud" Moore - 1948-1993; William A "Bill" Moore - 1993-2013
  - Hoffa Shadowbox containing buttons, ribbons, photographs belonging to Bill Moore, 1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Item 7)
    Father's Day Gift to Bill Moore, 1999
- Transfered Artifacts, 1930-2016; Series 8
  - Teamster Horse Accessories, ND (Box 28)
    This box contains some horse accessories, including a saddle and stirrups.
  - Miscellaneous Logo Artifacts, ND (Box 30)
    This box contains an IBT logo clock, Ron Carey desk display, and a Rhoe & Co. Inc, New York sign.
  - Miscellaneous Artifacts, ND (Box 13)
    This box contains miscellaenous Teamsters artifacts, including logo playing cards, small clocks, notepads, photo displays, and more.
  - Teamsters Pins with Duplicates, 1998-2011 (Box 14)
    This box contains Teamsters pins with duplicates. The pins in this box include: Vote Hoffa (1998), Teamsters local 120 2008 and 2011, Friend of Hoffa, local 129, and various logo pins.
  - Local Union Bibles, 1990's (Box 15)
    This box contains 4 Bibles, including one Bible engraved with Teamsters Local 554.
  - Glassware and Dishware (Box 16)
    This box contains glassware and dishware, both for functional and display purposes.
  - Hats, ND (Box 17)
    This box contains Teamsters baseball hats.
  - Miscellaneous Wearable Accessories, ND (Box 18)
    This box contains miscellaneous wearable accessories, including: watches, lanyards, patches, keychains, and more.
  - Clothing, ND (Box 19)
    This box contains Teamsters clothing including t-shirts, polo shirts, jackets, and convention delegate vests.
  - Pins, ND (Box 20)
    This box contains a large amount of miscellaneous pins, including delegate pins, logo pins, dues pins, and political pins.
  - Pins, ND (Box 21)
    This box contains various Teamsters pins, including delegate pins, logo pins, dues pins, and political pins. Some pins are in display cases.
  - Decals and Stickers (Box 22)
    This box contains various Teamsters stickers and decals.
  - Hurricane Katrina Teamsters Helping Teamsters Brick, 2005 (Box 23)
  - Baseball Uniform, ND (Box 24)
    This box contains the pants and socks portion of a baseball uniform.
  - 22nd Convention Briefcase, 1981 (Box 25)
    This box contains a briefcase from the 22nd international convention. In the briefcase are convention materials, such as a stack of cards, convention programs, and a convention plaque.
  - Tote Bags, ND (Box 26)
    This box contains miscellaneous Teamsters tote bags.
  - United States Bicentennial Silver Dishware, 1976 (Box 27)
  - Teamsters Poker Set and Wax Seals (Box 29)
  - IBT Crest Patches, ND; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Report of Rules Committee Proposed Convention Rules, ND; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Dunes, Las Vegas Hotel and Country Club, from Twenty-Second Convention Teamster Tag, 1981; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Officers' Report to the 22nd international Convention, 1981; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Twenty-Second International Convention, Leather bound notebook and pen, June 1981; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Plaque in Commemoration of The International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Twenty-Second Convention hosted by Western Conference IBT, 1976 June; Series 8 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - IBT Pack of Cards, ND; Series 8 (Box 33, Folder 2)